https://www.beginnings.ca/legal/

Terms and Conditions
Below you will find information relating to 1) the website terms of service, and 2) the website privacy policy. Beginnings Family Services is committed to upholding the highest standards in website security and confidentiality, and the following information was carefully designed to protect the interests of our valued clients and Beginnings Family Services as a whole.
TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SERVICE FOR THIS WEBSITE
PLEASE READ ALL OF THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SERVICE FOR THIS WEB SITE (“TCS”) BEFORE USING THIS SITE. By continuing to access, link to, or use this site, or any service on this site, you signify YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE TCS. Beginnings Family Services Limited (“BFS”) reserves the right to amend, remove, or add to the TCS at any time. Such modifications shall be effective immediately. Accordingly, please continue to review the TCS whenever accessing, linking to, or using this site. Your access, link to, or use of the site, or any service on this site, after the posting of modifications to the TCS will constitute YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE TCS, as modified. If, at any time, you do not wish to accept the TCS, you may not access, link to, or use the site. Any terms and conditions proposed by you which are in addition to or which conflict with the TCS are expressly rejected by BFS and shall be of no force or effect.
You represent that you have read and agree to be bound by the TCS.
Intellectual Property.  This Web site, including but not limited to text, content, photographs, and goods (the “Service”), is protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, international treaties, and/or other proprietary rights and laws of Canada and other countries. The Service is also protected as a collective work or compilation under Canadian copyright and other laws and treaties. All individual postings and other elements making up the Service are also copyrighted works. You agree to abide by all applicable copyright and other laws, as well as any additional copyright notices or restrictions contained in the Service. You acknowledge that the Service has been developed, compiled, prepared, revised, selected, and arranged by BFS, its general and limited partners, and its subsidiaries, and their respective general partners and affiliates (collectively “Beginnings”) and others (including certain other information sources) through the application of methods and standards of judgment developed and applied through the expenditure of substantial time, effort, and money and constitutes valuable intellectual property of Beginnings and such others. You agree to protect the proprietary rights of Beginnings and all others having rights in the Service and to comply with all reasonable written requests made by BFS or its suppliers and licensors of content, equipment, or otherwise (“Suppliers”) to protect their and others’ contractual, statutory, and common law rights in the Service. You agree to notify BFS in writing promptly upon becoming aware of any unauthorized access or use of the Service by any individual or entity or of any claim that the Service infringes upon any copyright, trademark, or other contractual, statutory, or common law rights. All present and future rights in and to trade secrets, patents, copyrights, trademarks, service marks, know-how, and other proprietary rights of any type under the laws of any governmental authority, domestic or foreign, including rights in and to all applications and registrations relating to the Service (the “Intellectual Property Rights”) shall, as between you and Beginnings, at all times be and remain the sole and exclusive property of Beginnings. All present and future rights in and title to the Service (including the right to exploit the Service and any portions of the Service over any present or future technology) are reserved to Beginnings for its exclusive use. Except as specifically permitted by the TCS, you may not copy or make any use of the Service or any portion thereof. Except as specifically permitted herein, you shall not use the Intellectual Property Rights or the Service, or the names of any individual participant in, or contributor to, the Service, or any variations or derivatives thereof, for any purpose, without BFS’s prior written approval.
Restrictions on Use. YOU MAY NOT USE THE SERVICE FOR ANY ILLEGAL PURPOSE OR IN ANY MANNER INCONSISTENT WITH THE TCS. YOU AGREE TO USE THE SERVICE SOLELY FOR YOUR OWN NONCOMMERCIAL USE AND BENEFIT, AND NOT FOR RESALE OR OTHER TRANSFER OR DISPOSITION TO, OR USE BY OR FOR THE BENEFIT OF, ANY OTHER PERSON OR ENTITY. YOU AGREE NOT TO USE, TRANSFER, DISTRIBUTE, OR DISPOSE OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THE SERVICE IN ANY MANNER THAT COULD COMPETE WITH THE BUSINESS OF BEGINNINGS OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS. YOU MAY NOT COPY, REPRODUCE, RECOMPILE, DECOMPILE, DISASSEMBLE, REVERSE ENGINEER, DISTRIBUTE, PUBLISH, DISPLAY, PERFORM, MODIFY, UPLOAD TO, CREATE DERIVATIVE WORKS FROM, TRANSMIT, OR IN ANY WAY EXPLOIT ANY PART OF THE SERVICE, EXCEPT THAT YOU MAY DOWNLOAD MATERIAL FROM THE SERVICE AND/OR MAKE ONE PRINT COPY FOR YOUR OWN PERSONAL, NONCOMMERCIAL USE, PROVIDED THAT YOU RETAIN ALL COPYRIGHT AND OTHER PROPRIETARY NOTICES. YOU MAY NOT RECIRCULATE, REDISTRIBUTE OR PUBLISH THE ANALYSIS AND PRESENTATION INCLUDED IN THE SERVICE WITHOUT BFS’S PRIOR WRITTEN CONSENT. MODIFICATION OF THE SERVICE’S CONTENT WOULD BE A VIOLATION OF THE COPYRIGHTS AND OTHER PROPRIETARY RIGHTS OF BFS AND/OR BEGINNINGS FAMILY SERVICES LIMITED OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES. ADDITIONALLY, YOU MAY NOT OFFER ANY PART OF THE SERVICE FOR SALE OR DISTRIBUTE IT OVER ANY OTHER MEDIUM INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO OVER-THE-AIR TELEVISION OR RADIO BROADCAST, A COMPUTER NETWORK OR HYPERLINK FRAMING ON THE INTERNET WITHOUT THE PRIOR WRITTEN CONSENT OF BFS. THE SERVICE AND THE INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREIN MAY NOT BE USED TO CONSTRUCT A DATABASE OF ANY KIND. NOR MAY THE SERVICE BE STORED (IN ITS ENTIRETY OR IN ANY PART) IN DATABASES FOR ACCESS BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY OR TO DISTRIBUTE ANY DATABASE SERVICES CONTAINING ALL OR PART OF THE SERVICE. FURTHERMORE, YOU MAY NOT USE ANY OF THE TRADEMARKS, TRADE NAMES, SERVICE MARKS, COPYRIGHTS, OR LOGOS OF BEGINNINGS FAMILY SERVICES LIMITED OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES IN ANY MANNER WHICH CREATES THE IMPRESSION THAT SUCH ITEMS BELONG TO OR ARE ASSOCIATED WITH YOU OR, EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE PROVIDED HEREIN, ARE USED WITH BFS’S CONSENT, AND YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE NO OWNERSHIP RIGHTS IN AND TO ANY OF SUCH ITEMS. YOU WILL NOT USE THE SERVICE OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREIN IN UNSOLICITED MAILINGS OR SPAM MATERIAL. YOU WILL NOT USE ANY TRADEMARKS, TRADE NAMES, SERVICE MARKS, COPYRIGHTS, OR LOGOS OF BEGINNINGS FAMILY SERVIVES LIMITED OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES IN UNSOLICITED MAILINGS OR SPAM MATERIAL. YOU WILL NOT SPAM OR SEND UNSOLICITED MAILINGS TO ANY PERSON OR ENTITY USING THE SERVICE. YOU AGREE TO COMPLY WITH ANY OTHER APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SERVICE SET FORTH ON THE SERVICE.
WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT
Beginnings does not share, rent or sell personally identifiable information collected on the website to other individuals, corporations or organizations.
Use of Cookies. Beginnings reserves the right to use cookies or similar electronic tools to collect anonymous information to improve the website for its valued users. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer and which collects information about your use of this Web site, such as the Web pages visited, the date and the time of a visit, the Web sites you visited immediately before and after visiting this Web site, etc. Any information collected by the cookies used by Beginnings would be collected anonymously and would not be used by Beginnings to subsequently identify you or to prepare the collection, processing, or use of personal information about you. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to disable cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. The help function on most browsers contains instructions on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies or to disable cookies entirely.
Links To Third-Party Web Sites. Beginnings may provide links to third-party Web sites. As we do not control third-party sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those Web sites before providing any of your personal information on such sites.
Modifications To This Privacy Policy. Beginnings reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions on this Web page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.
Further Information: Contact Us at Head Office
1.877.528.6665
Follow Beginnings
Beginnings is a non-profit agency, with registered charitable status (CCRA Charitable Reg. No. 11880 2388 RR0001).
©2020 Beginnings Family Services. All rights reserved.
